NLRB Oral History Project II Master Tapes 5843 OHM
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NLRB Oral History Project II Master Tapes
1989-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Labor Relations Board (NLRB)
5843 OHM
11.67 cubic feet
1 file folder.
Interviews, audiiovisual materials.
8620880
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 06, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3001: Jean T. McKelvey Papers /3007: Maurice Neufeld Papers /3013: Christopher Lindley Papers /3036: Robert Raimon Papers /3051: Albert Martin Papers /4039: Milton R. Konvitz Papers /4040: George H. Hildebrand Papers /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4057 AV: James A. Gross NLRB Audiocassettes /4057 P: James A. Gross NLRB Photographs /4064: Kurt Hanslowe Papers /4073: James O. Morris Office Files /4085: Milton R. Konvitz Additional Papers /4107: Kheel Center Additional Cataloging Project Work notes /4117 P: ILR School Photographs /4124: James A. Gross Papers, Additional NLRB Research Files /4148: George W. Brooks Additional Papers /4162: Kheel Center Additional Special Projects Files /4166: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Files /4166 AV: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Audio-Visual Materials /4186: James A. Gross Additional Research Files /4190: James A. Gross Additional Research Files /4191 F: ILR School Audio-Visual Department Films /4212: Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence /4232: James A. Gross Collection of NLRB 60th Annual Conference Files /4256: ILR Press Article Reprints and Promotional Materials /4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Audio-Visual Materials 5011: Morton Singer Papers 5016: Cornell University Union Representation Material 5034: Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5073: U.S. Board of Inquiry to Report on Certain Labor Disputes Affecting the Maritime Industry of the United States Records 5141: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records 5175: Jacob Seidenberg Taft-Hartley Maritime Dispute Records 5204 mf: Southern Tenant Farmers Union Records on Microfilm
United States. National Labor Board.
8620880
- Frank McCulloch - 9/1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch: 9/1989 -- tape 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch: 9/1989 -- tape 3 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch: 9/1989 -- tape 4 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch: 9/1989 -- tape 5 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch: 9/1989 -- tape 6 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch: 9/1989 -- tape 7 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch: 9/1989 -- tape 8 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch: 9/1989 -- tape 9 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch: 9/1989 -- tape 10 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch: 9/1989 -- tape 11 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Frank McCulloch: 9/1989 -- tape 12 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- H. Stephan Gordon: tape 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- H. Stephan Gordon: tape 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- H. Stephan Gordon: tape 3 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- H. Stephan Gordon: tape 4 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- H. Stephan Gordon: tape 5 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Peter Nash: tape 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Peter Nash: tape 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Peter Nash: tape 3 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Peter Nash: tape 4 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Peter Nash: tape 5 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Warren Davison: tape 1 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Warren Davison: tape 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Warren Davison: tape 3 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Ken McGuiness: tape 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Ken McGuiness: tape 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Ken McGuiness: tape 3 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Ken McGuiness: tape 4 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Joseph DeSio: tape 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Joseph DeSio: tape 2 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Daniel H. Pollitt - 9/1989: tape 1 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Daniel H. Pollitt - 9/1989: tape 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Daniel H. Pollitt - 9/1989: tape 3 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Daniel H. Pollitt - 9/1989: tape 4 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Mozart Ratner: tape 1 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Mozart Ratner: tape 2 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Mozart Ratner: tape 3 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Mozart Ratner: tape 4 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Mozart Ratner: tape 5 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Mozart Ratner: tape 6 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Howard Jenkins: tape 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Howard Jenkins: tape 2 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Howard Jenkins: tape 3 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Howard Jenkins: tape 4 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- John Truesdale: tape 1 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- John Truesdale: tape 2 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- John Truesdale: tape 3 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Roman Pucinski - tape 1 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Roman Pucinski - tape 2 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Thomas W. Miller, Jr.: tape 1 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Thomas W. Miller, Jr.: tape 2 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Ralph Winkler - tape 1 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Ralph Winkler - tape 2 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Michael Walsh: tape 1 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Michael Walsh: tape 2 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Marcel Mallet-Prevost: tape 1 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Marcel Mallet-Prevost: tape 2 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Douglas Soutar Oral History Interview - Nov. 16, 1990: #1175 - tape 1 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Douglas Soutar Oral History Interview - Nov. 16, 1990: #1175 - tape 2 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Douglas Soutar Oral History Interview - Nov. 16, 1990: #1175 - tape 3 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Lester Asher - tape 1 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Lester Asher - tape 2 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Lester Asher - tape 3 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Berton Subrin: tape 1 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Berton Subrin: tape 2 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Berton Subrin: tape 3 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Berton Subrin: tape 4 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Theophil Kammholz: tape 1 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Theophil Kammholz: tape 2 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Melvin Welles: tape 1 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Melvin Welles: tape 2 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Melvin Welles: tape 3 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Melvin Welles: tape 4 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Melvin Welles: tape 5 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Gerald Brown: tape 1 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Gerald Brown: tape 2 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Gerald Brown: tape 3 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Gerald Brown: tape 4 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Wm. Feldesman - tape 1 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Wm. Feldesman - tape 2 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Wm. Feldesman - tape 3 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Wm. Feldesman - tape 4 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- A. Norman Somers: tape 1 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- A. Norman Somers: tape 2 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- A. Norman Somers: tape 3 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- John Higgins: tape 1 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- John Higgins: tape 2 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Norton Come: tape 1 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Norton Come: tape 2 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Norton Come: tape 3 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Norton Come: tape 4 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Norton Come: tape 5 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Norton Come: tape 6 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Norton Come: tape 7 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Norton Come: tape 8 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Norton Come: tape 9 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Norton Come: tape 10 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Sam Zagoria: tape 1 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Sam Zagoria: tape 2 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Sam Zagoria: tape 3 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Sam Zagoria: tape 4 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Frank Kleiler: tape 1 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Frank Kleiler: tape 2 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Frank Kleiler: tape 3 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Audio digitized from the collection. (Box 106)